<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:schema="http://schema.org/" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#" version="2.0" xml:base="https://cnsnews.com/feed/autotweet/1">
  <channel>
    <title>CNS AutoTweet 1</title>
    <link>https://cnsnews.com/feed/autotweet/1</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Lt. Col. @AllenWest sees similarities between actions of American mobs and ISIS</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/blog/andrew-davenport/lt-col-west-no-difference-between-american-mobs-and-isis-statue-toppling</link>
  <description>
A statue of Confederate States President Jefferson Davis lies on the street after protesters pulled it down in Richmond, Va., on June 10, 2020. (Photo credit: PARKER MICHELS-BOYCE/AFP via Getty Images)


Lt. Col Allen West criticized mobs tearing down statues for becoming almost "seditious," comparing their actions to the Taliban and ISIS while speaking with Mark Levin on Levin's Fox News show, "Life, Liberty, and Levin" on Sunday.

“When you have people that are going on air, and they are saying that if our demands are not met, we are going to burn the system down, when you have individuals who are going into a major urban population center and they are declaring an autonomous zone, when you have people that are destroying monuments and memorials and going after our history and our traditions, there is no difference between what we see happening in America right now than what the Taliban did in Bamyan province in Afghanistan and what ISIS did in northern Iraq and also in Syria in establishing the caliphate," West said.

The lieutenant colonel and former Florida Republican congressman emphasized the importance of the rule of law in America. 

“Well, what we are seeing in the United States of America is an ideological civil war, and we are seeing people that have gone beyond that constitutional right of freedom of speech, and freedom of expression, and the right to petition their government for redress of grievances," he said. "And this now has almost become sedition."



Below is a transcript of this part of the segment:

Levin:


"You've been around a while. You've seen combat. You've seen some of our cities burning. You've seen riots. You've seen the media, how they've been reporting on this. You see how Democrat mayors are conducting themselves. You see how the Democrat leadership is conducting itself. What -- just give us generally, what is your feeling about what you're seeing."


West:


“Well what we are seeing in the United States of America is an ideological civil war, and we are seeing people that have gone beyond that constitutional right of freedom of speech, and freedom of expression, and the right to petition their government for redress of grievances. And this now has almost become sedition. This is about undermining the very foundation and fundamental principles and values of these great United States of America as a constitutional republic. 

When you have people that are going on air, and they are saying that if our demands are not met, we are going to burn the system down, when you have individuals who are going into a major urban population center and they are declaring an autonomous zone, when you have people that are destroying monuments and memorials and going after our history and our traditions, there is no difference between what we see happening in America right now than what the Taliban did in Bamyan province in Afghanistan and what ISIS did in northern Iraq and also in Syria in establishing the caliphate.

It’s the exact same thing with establishing these autonomous zones. This comes down to one simple choice that we all have to make. Do we stand for the rule of law, or are we going to allow mob rule in the United States of America?”


Andrew Davenport is a student at Regent University, where he studies political communication and American politics. He has served as the chairman of the Regent Young Americans for Freedom and a student alumni ambassador since 2018. He is a member of the National Journalism Center program and serves as the senior representative of Regent University student government. Following his undergraduate, he plans to pursue an M.A. in government focusing on public policy.   
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 15:38</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Andrew Davenport</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158985</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>NYPD Officers’ Retirement Filings Up 49 Percent Since George Floyd’s Death</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/blog/melanie-arter/nypd-officers-retirement-filings-49-percent-george-floyds-death</link>
  <description>
 



NYPD's Mounted Unit patrol officers stand in front of the Pride and Black Lives Matter billboards in Times Square on June 22, 2020 in New York City. Due to the ongoing coronavirus pandemic, this year's Pride march had to be canceled over health concerns. The annual event, which sees millions of attendees, marks it's 50th anniversary since the first march following the Stonewall Inn riots. (Photo by Noam Galai/Getty Images)


Hundreds of NYPD officers have filed for retirement in the weeks after George Floyd’s death through June 23, almost 50 percent more than last year.

A total of 272 officers filed for retirement during that time period – a 49 percent increase over the same time period in 2019, the New York Post reports. Last year, 183 officers file for retirement during that time.

"We are all asking the same question: ‘How can we keep doing our job in this environment?’" Police Benevolent Association President Patrick Lynch told the New York Post. "And that is exactly what the anti-cop crowd wants. If we have no cops because no one wants to be a cop, they will have achieved their ultimate goal.”

According to Police Benevolent Association President Patrick Lynch, officers are at their “breaking point.”

"We are all asking the same question: ‘How can we keep doing our job in this environment?’" he told the New York Post. "And that is exactly what the anti-cop crowd wants. If we have no cops because no one wants to be a cop, they will have achieved their ultimate goal.”

Ed Mullins, president of the Sergeants Benevolent Association, said that nearly 80 of his members have recently filed for retirement and morale is at the lowest levels he’s seen in 38 years.

“People have had enough and no longer feel it’s worth risking their personal well-being for a thankless position,” Mullins said.

“There is no leadership, no direction, no training for new policies,” he said. “Department brass is paralyzed (and) too afraid to uphold their sworn oath in fear of losing their jobs. Sadly, the people of this city will soon experience what New York City was like in the 1980s.
”
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 14:37</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Melanie Arter</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158984</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Minneapolis City Council Votes to Abolish PD; Some Members Have Private Security</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/blog/john-jakubisin/minneapolis-city-council-votes-abolish-pd-some-members-have-private-security</link>
  <description>
MANHATTAN, NY - JUNE 19: An African American protester wears a mask and holds a homemade sign that says, "Defund the Police" as they perform a peaceful protest walk across the Brooklyn Bridge. (Photo by Ira L. Black/Corbis via Getty Images)


Minneapolis City Council voted 12-0 in favor of abolishing the Minneapolis Police Department on Friday. Meanwhile, the city recently hired private security for three of the council members, costing taxpayers $4,500 a day.

The council unanimously approved an amendment which would rewrite the city charter. It will now be submitted to the popular vote. The amendment will remove the city’s police department from the charter of the city and put in its place a new Charter Department that would “provide for community safety and violence prevention.”

The new department would “have responsibility for public safety services prioritizing a holistic, public health-oriented approach.”

The City of Minneapolis also hired private security for three of its council members, which has cost the city around $63,000 over the past three weeks, beginning approximately June 8, according to Fox 9.

The security detail is for council members Andrea Jenkins, Phillipe Cunningham, and Alondra Cano, who have all been vocal advocates for defunding and abolishing the police department and who have received death threats.

When Fox 9 asked why the Minneapolis Police Department was not providing the security, a city spokesperson responded that the MPD resources are needed in the community.

The city council’s move to dismantle the police department comes after weeks of protest following the death of George Floyd, who died after an encounter with Minneapolis police.

Although concentrated in Minneapolis, calls for “defunding” or “abolishing” police have been widespread across the country.

Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey has publicly opposed calls for “abolishing” the police. A spokesperson for the mayor’s office said the mayor is “unwavering in his commitment to working with Chief Arradondo toward deep structural reforms and uprooting systemic racism. He does not support abolishing the police department,” according to CNN.
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 13:42</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>John Jakubisin</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158983</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>“A mask is not a political statement. It’s an IQ test.”</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/bailey-duran/does-wearing-mask-mean-you-are-smarter-those-who-dont</link>
  <description>
House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) (Getty Images) 


(CNS News) – As face masks become a societal norm, many people are speaking out against those who are choosing not to wear them, and some critics say that wearing a mask may determine how smart you are.

John Lundin, a self-described environmental activist and author, recently tweeted, “A mask is not a political statement. It’s an IQ test.” His tweet was met with many comments of support.


(Twitter.)


A recent Gallup/Knight Foundation poll that asked, “In the past 7 days, how often did you wear a mask or cloth face covering outside your home?” showed that 30% of high school graduates, 41% of college graduates and 46% of postgraduates always wear masks.

This poll also showed that 49% of Democrats always wear masks compared to the 26% of Republicans who do. 

Pavel Blagov, associate professor of psychology at Whitman College, went even further by doing a study to show that people who do not wear masks may have psychopathic or “Dark Triad” traits. Dark Triad refers to narcissism, Machiavellianism, and psychopathy.


(Gallup/Knight Foundation)


"One potential implication from this research is that there may be a minority of people with particular personality styles (on the narcissism and psychopathy spectrum) that have a disproportionate impact on the pandemic by failing to protect themselves and others," Blagov said.

His study only gathered information about a select group of adults in the United States, so its findings don’t accurately represent all people and age groups.

The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) encourages people to wear face masks when they leave their home. They specifically urge people to wear cloth or fabric face masks in order to save surgical and N95 masks for health professionals.

The CDC says that the “cloth face covering may not protect the wearer, but it may keep the wearer from spreading the virus to others.”


(Getty Images)


According to Live Science, experts say that fabric masks “might” help curb the spread of COVID-19, but that it is not confirmed if they actually make a noticeable difference.

May Chu, a professor of epidemiology at the Colorado School of Public Health, says that “homemade fabric masks are the least effective,” because they only “impede 2% of airflow.”

According to multiple tests, wearing a fabric mask does not prevent the user from getting the virus. It may not even prevent a person with COVID from infecting others.

A study published by Annals of Internal Medicine showed that cloth masks do not effectively stop the spread of the virus through airborne pathogens. In the study, people who had tested positive for COVID-19 were asked to cough into a petri dish—once without a mask, once with a surgical mask and once with a fabric mask.

Neither one of the masks kept the virus particles from being coughed into the petri dish. Despite these findings, the journal retracted the study soon after it was published.  

Wearing masks is even becoming a political statement as Nancy Pelosi urged the CDC to require all Americans to wear masks. Pelosi says this kind of ruling is “long overdue” and even went as far as to speculate that the CDC had not required masks so they would “not offend” President Trump.

Vice President Mike Pence, head of the coronavirus task force, says they believe people should wear masks but specified that people should wear masks “wherever social distancing is not possible.”

Washington State Governor Jay Inslee (D) spoke to CBS of his disgust that President Donald Trump has not tweeted about the importance of masks, and instead has tweeted about monuments destroyed by radical protesters.

“Now we need a president who will care more about living Americans and less about dead Confederates,” Inslee said.
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 13:16</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Bailey Duran</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158982</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>The states legalizing weed better read this...</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/commentary/john-stonestreet/link-between-marijuana-psychosis-and-suicide</link>
  <description>
Individuals purchase marijuana following its legalization. (Photo credit: KAMIL KRZACZYNSKI/AFP via Getty Images)


Recreational marijuana is legal in 11 states and more than 20 more states permit the use of so-called “medical marijuana.”

I say “so-called” because, as NYU drug policy expert Mark Kleinman has put it, “the vast majority of ‘patients’ buying ‘medical marijuana’ aren’t doing so under any sort of active medical supervision....Many of them aren’t ‘treating’ anything but their desire to get high.”

In the push to legalize, America has been sold dangerous lies about marijuana – of financial windfalls with no accompanying social cost and of therapeutic benefits with no accompanying dangers. But marijuana is dangerous. In fact, for some, it’s potentially lethal.

Dr. Erik Messamore, a psychiatrist with a doctorate in psychopharmacology, recently brought attention to a study published by a branch of NIH about my state, which is ground zero of the marijuana push in the United States. The title of the study telegraphs the punchline: “Legalized Cannabis in Colorado Emergency Departments: A Cautionary Review of Negative Health and Safety Effects.”

This “cautionary review” begins rather bluntly: “Cannabis legalization has led to significant health consequences, particularly to patients in emergency departments and hospitals in Colorado.” The consequences that are, in their words, “most concerning” are “psychosis, suicide, and other substance abuse,” not to mention the impairment of a user’s “complex decision-making,” which may be irreversible, even by subsequent abstinence.

In Colorado, cannabis-related emergency and urgent-care visits among “teenagers and young adults” increased nearly three-fold after legalization. Most of these visits required “behavioral health evaluation.”

To quote the G.I. Joe public service announcements of my youth, “Now you know, and knowing is half the battle.” Except, and this should disturb us all, the link between cannabis use and mental illness was already well-known before legalization.

In his book, No One Cares About Crazy People, Ron Powers (who co-wrote the World War II history Flags of Our Fathers) told the story of his two sons, both diagnosed with schizophrenia in their early twenties. Marijuana use, Powers learned, contributed to their diagnosis. Specifically, marijuana use increases the chances of schizophrenia for people who carry the genes AKT1 and COMT, which “affect brain chemistry.” Powers’ sons had these genes. One of them committed suicide, and the other attempted suicide but was saved through a timely intervention.

Again, all of this was known in 2014 when Colorado eagerly legalized cannabis. It’s still known today, even as legal weed marches across the rest of the country.

By the way, do you know what is also known? The claim that you can somehow limit marijuana use to adults who are just looking to relax or get high, and keep it away from kids and schools, is, well, excrement. Even before legalization, teenagers had no problem getting marijuana. Are we supposed to believe that legalization has made it more difficult?

And, how are we supposed to keep those with the triggering genes from using? Unless there’s a known family history of schizophrenia, chances are the first time someone knows they have AKT1 or COMT is after they land in the psych ward.

Despite what we know about the effects of marijuana use on teenage brains and the genetic-related danger to some, we are committed to playing Russian Roulette with young lives. And media outlets loudly proclaim legalization as “inevitable” and part of our expanding “freedom,” even while stories about the hazards go underreported.

By the way, this “cautionary review” was published a year ago. I only heard about it recently. It clearly escaped the attention of just about everyone, including those tasked with knowing.

Given all the talk of listening to scientists and experts about COVID-19, climate change, and all kinds of other subjects, why are we ignoring the clear data on this? If there are links (and there are) between cannabis, psychosis, and suicide, especially with teenagers and young adults, there should be no more discussion. Wanting to get high is no excuse for allowing others to be hurt.

John Stonestreet is President of The Chuck Colson Center for Christian Worldview and BreakPoint co-host. Roberto Rivera is a Senior Writer and Fellow at the Colson Center. Since joining BreakPoint and the Colson Center's predecessor in 1995, he has written almost 2,000 commentaries, several book introductions, and hundreds of columns.

Editor's Note: This piece originally appeared on BreakPoint.
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 12:37</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>John Stonestreet and Roberto Rivera</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158981</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>NYC homicide rate hits 5-year high...</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/nyc-shootings-top-500-ytd-city-looks-cut-1-billion-police-budget</link>
  <description>
(Getty Images/Noam Galai)


More than five hundred people have been shot in New York City so far this year, but the city is considering cutting the New York City Police Department’s (NYPD) budget by as much as $1 billion.

Through Saturday, shootings have surpassed the five hundred mark, with 17 taking place on Saturday alone, local affiliate ABC 7 reports:


“17 shootings occurred in New York City Saturday, highlighting an alarming rise in gun violence across the City. Through Saturday, the City has seen more than 500 shootings year to date. Gun violence has ramped up considerably this month. Between June 19-27, 83 shootings happened, injuring or killing 112 people.”




There were 100 shootings in May and at least 58 shootings in the week leading up to the last weekend, while the city’s homicide rate has hit a five-year high, increasing 42% year-to-date. Still, the city is considering proposals to make a drastic cut in the NYPD budget  CBS affiliate WLNY reports:


“This is happening as city government debates whether to slash the department’s budget by up to $1 billion to reallocate funding to youth outreach and other education programs.”

</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 12:27</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Craig Bannister</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158980</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Snopes caught with its pants down...shocker!</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/commentary/hans-bader/supposed-truth-arbiter-snopes-misstates-qualified-immunity-law</link>
  <description>
A sculpture of a gavel is featured outside the Supreme Court of Ohio. (Photo credit: Raymond Boyd/Getty Images)


Snopes is supposedly a myth-busting web site. But occasionally, it promotes myths of its own.

For example, it recently made false claims about the legal doctrine of qualified immunity, which was invented by the courts in 1967. Snopes falsely claimed that this immunity blocks lawsuits over a constitutional violation, unless a court has previously found a violation in "nearly identical" circumstances. It also falsely claimed that qualified immunity would likely hinder George Floyd's family in winning a wrongful death lawsuit over his killing.

Neither of these claims is true. Qualified immunity does not apply when a government official commits a violation of "clearly established" constitutional rights. That includes violations that are so outrageous or unique that no prior court ruling could ever have dealt with "nearly identical" facts. Such violations are nevertheless deemed "clearly established" and grounds for denying qualified immunity. As the Supreme Court explained in United States v. Lanier (1997), “The easiest cases don’t even arise. There has never been...a section 1983 case accusing welfare officials of selling foster children into slavery; it does not follow that if such a case arose, the officials would be immune from damages [or criminal] liability.'”

Lawyers who sue police departments have said that the slow killing of George Floyd was a violation of his clearly-established constitutional rights. An officer killing a non‐​resisting suspect by kneeling on his neck for a long period of time while the suspect says he can’t breathe, is a clear violation of the right to be free of excessive use of force. Police who murder someone also violate the clear language of the Fourteenth Amendment's due process clause, which protects the right to "life" against arbitrary deprivation.  As the civil-rights lawyer Chris Wiest noted, “I do civil rights cases. And I sue police. I assure you, there is no qualified immunity in [the Floyd] case for the officers involved on these facts with the video evidence.”

Yet, here is how Scopes describes qualified immunity:


"Viral video of former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin pressing his knee into the neck of George Floyd, a Black man, for nearly nine minutes before his death resulted in widespread outrage and weeks of civil rights protests across the U.S. Amid a groundswell of popular pressure, prosecutors took the unusual step of arresting and charging Chauvin with second-degree murder and also charging three other officers at the scene with aiding and abetting him.

But even if Chauvin is found guilty, attorneys we spoke to who are experts in a legal doctrine called 'qualified immunity' told us it would still be an uphill battle for Floyd’s family to successfully sue for restitution.

That’s because qualified immunity, though obscure, is a significant legal hurdle for civilians who try to sue police for claims of constitutional violations, such as the Fourth Amendment protection against unlawful search and seizure, when police kill or injure someone. To get past it, plaintiffs in lawsuits have to show that the exact manner in which a police officer violated their rights has been 'clearly established' as wrongful by legal precedent. That means they must be able to point to another court case with circumstances nearly identical to theirs, and in which a court ruled that an officer had violated the Constitution."


But plaintiffs don't have to point to another case "with circumstances nearly identical to theirs." The fact that a cop has chosen to abuse you in a novel way doesn't mean courts will grant him qualified immunity, and it doesn't mean it doesn't count as "excessive use of force." For example, the fact that cops previously violated the Constitution by beating or shooting the people they arrested didn't keep the Ninth Circuit from denying qualified immunity to cops who put pepper spray in people's eyes. The fact that police chose a novel way to use excessive force didn't prevent the judges from finding it was still a violation of "clearly established" constitutional rights. (See Headwaters Forest Defense v. Cty. of Humboldt, 276 F.3d 1125 (9th Cir. 2002)).

Similarly, a federal appeals court recently ruled that prison officials violated clearly established constitutional rights if they failed to remove items from an inmate's cell that he could use to hang himself. It allowed the officials to be sued, even though the appeals court had never before confronted nearly identical circumstances, and it ruled the prison officials could be sued even if they did not intend specifically to cause the inmate's death. (See Converse v. City of Kemah (2020)).

Similarly, an appeals court allowed a man's estate to sue the police for unnecessarily shooting him, even though he allegedly possessed a knife, and had resisted arrest, in Estate of Jones v. City of Martinsburg (2020).

By contrast, George Floyd was not resisting arrest and was not carrying a weapon. Floyd's estate would thus have an easier time suing, and an even easier time defeating a claim of qualified immunity.

So the doctrine of qualified immunity is not a license to murder people.

It is nonetheless controversial, for good reason. It was made up by judges in a 1967 Supreme Court ruling. It is not even mentioned in the text of 42 U.S.C. 1983, the law that qualified immunity was read into, which simply allows lawsuits over violations of constitutional and federal statutory rights. It also has no common-law pedigree, unlike other defenses like the doctrine of judicial immunity. Judges like Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas have sensibly argued that qualified immunity should be abolished by the Supreme Court.

Qualified immunity doesn't just apply to police officers. It applies to all government officials. It is frequently used to prevent students at state universities from suing for restitution or other compensation for unconstitutional speech restrictions, as Samantha Harris of the Foundation for Individual Rights in Education notes. Courts sometimes misapply the doctrine to block lawsuits for compensation, even if it is rather obvious that the student's speech was protected and should not have led to discipline, simply because the Supreme Court and federal appeals court for the region in which the student is suing have not previously addressed a case involving strikingly similar facts.

If qualified immunity is abolished -- as it probably should be -- it should be abolished for all government officials, not just police officers.

Hans Bader practices law in Washington, D.C. After studying economics and history at the University of Virginia and law at Harvard, he practiced civil-rights, international-trade, and constitutional law. He also once worked in the Education Department.
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 11:35</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Hans Bader</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158978</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>'On both sides it’s tough, to try to figure this out.'</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/washington/andrew-davenport/sen-rick-scott-whether-biological-males-should-be-allowed-play</link>
  <description>
Sen. Rick Scott (R-Fla.). (Getty Images)


(CNS News) -- When asked whether biological males who identify as females should be allowed to play girls' sports, Sen. Rick Scott (R-Fla.) said it was a “tough issue” to figure out and he would need to “think about it a lot more.”

At the Capitol on June 24, CNS News asked Senator Scott, “When the House Judiciary Committee considered the Equality Act it rejected an amendment that said the act would not require biological females to face biological males in sports competition. So, should biological males who say they identify as females be allowed to play girls’ sports?”  





The senator said, “Yeah, I think this is a really tough issue. On both sides it’s tough, to try to figure this out. So, I need to think about it a lot more.”

The Equality Act was passed in the House on May 17, 2019. It was sent to the Senate where it has yet to be voted on. The bill prohibits “discrimination based on “sex, sexual orientation, and gender identity in a wide variety of areas including public accommodations and facilities, education, federal funding, employment, housing, credit, and the jury system.”

Rep. Greg Steube (R-Fla.) proposed an amendment to the Equality Act that would prevent forcing female athletes to compete with biological males. 


On left, transgender "female" cyclist Rachel McKinnon. (Getty Images)




During a call for a procedural vote on the amendment, Steube stated that nothing in the law “may be construed to diminish” existing protections under Title IX of the Civil Rights Act, which prohibits sex discrimination in education programs that receive federal funding. 

Title IX is a law that states, “No person in the United States shall, on the basis of sex, be excluded from participation in, be denied the benefits of, or be subjected to discrimination under any education program or activity receiving Federal financial assistance.”

In Connecticut, a transgender person who is a biological male set State Open records in the 100 and 200-meter race in early June 2018. 

In May 2019, a biological male who identified as a woman set records for age and weight class but was later stripped of the title as a power-lifter after receiving backlash. 


Transgender "female" soccer player Maria Gomez. (Getty Images)

</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 11:12</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Andrew Davenport</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158979</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Pastor: "We have to take some responsibility ourselves"...</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/chicago-pastor-calls-end-citys-no-snitch-policy-after-43-shot-13-killed</link>
  <description>
Pastor Corey Brooks

(Screenshot)


New Beginnings Church of Chicago Pastor Corey Brooks called for a three-step response to the violence in his city that took the lives of 13 people, including a one year-old child, last weekend.

First, his community needs to end its “no snitch” policy, Pastor Brooks said in a Monday interview with Fox &amp; Friends First:


“Well, we’re definitely not doing enough. We have to take some responsibility ourselves. In our community, we have a ‘no snitch’ policy and we have to get rid of that policy – that’s the first thing.”






Next, citizens who know the streets and are able to discourage violence need to become more active, and more mentorship programs need to be immediately instituted, the pastor said:



“And, the second thing we have to do is get violence interrupters and violence intervention actively engaged in the lives of these young men and on the streets.

“And, then the third thing we need to do is get mentoring programs really going early on, if we’re ever going to defeat this violent surge that we see every single day in our community.”

…

“We have to get more violence interrupters involved, violence engagers, those individuals who know about the streets, those individuals who know the shooters. We’ve got to get them involved, we’ve got to get them engaged and we need to do it immediately. And, the more we can get the better. We can’t wait on police officers to do all of the work for us. We have to engage our community and do a lot of the work ourselves.

“We do need all hands on deck, but we need to get everybody more engaged, because every single day we’re experiencing violence in the city of Chicago and it’s very, very disheartening.”

</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 11:00</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Craig Bannister</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158976</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Frieden: Opening When Cases Are Increasing, ‘Like Leaning into a Left Hook’</title>
  <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/melanie-arter/frieden-opening-when-cases-are-increasing-leaning-left-hook</link>
  <description>
Dr. Tom Frieden, former director of the Center for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), speaks about the Zika outbreak at the New America think tank in Washington, DC, on July 13, 2016. (Photo by SAUL LOEB/AFP via Getty Images)


(CNSNews.com) – Former Director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) Tom Frieden told “Fox News Sunday” that the United States is reopening too fast and “if you open when cases are still increasing … it’s like leaning into a left hook.”

When asked to explain the new surge in cases particularly in the South and the West and whether those regions opened too soon and without enough restrictions, Frieden said, “As I said to you six weeks ago today, this is going to backfire. We're moving too fast. If you open when cases are still increasing, as many states did, it's like leaning into a left hook. You're going to get hit hard, and that's what's happening.






“When we see Arizona, Texas, Florida, South Carolina, they are currently in a rapid upswing and sad to say, this is going to continue to get worse for weeks, because the physical distancing that they're implementing now will only take effect -- you won't see it for another few weeks, so we are going to see a few more weeks of increases in all likelihood in several states,” he said.

“Now, there's some comfort in the fact that it's younger people, but what starts in the young doesn't stay in the young. Younger people have parents, uncles, nephews. They go out to places to buy food, and we are going to see increasing spread. That's why the three W’s are so important: wear a mask, wash your hands or use sanitizer, and watch your distance," Frieden said.

There's something everyone can do. We are really all in this together, and if we work together we can help control the virus and get our economy back. Public health and health issues are not getting in the way of our recovery. They are the route to our recovery," the former CDC director said.

Frieden said the coronavirus has “the upper hand,” it’s “not going to go away on its own.”

“We have to stop it and only we can do that by working together, but we are all sick and tired of staying home, but you know what, the virus is not tired of making us sick, and what we're seeing, particularly in southern states, but in most parts of the U.S., is the virus increasing and in some states increasing explosively,” he said.

When asked whether the surge in COVID-19 cases is a function of more testing or a reflection of the fact that the virus is actually spreading, Frieden said, “As a doctor, scientist, an epidemiologist, I can tell you with 100 percent certainty that in most states where you're seeing an increase, it is a real increase. 

“It is not more tests. It is more spread of the virus, and the one number to look at that's very important is the percent of tests that's positive. The number of cases, that can vary some because we are only diagnosing 10, 20 percent of all cases. So the numbers you're seeing are just a reflection, a tip of the iceberg, of even more spread,” he said.

“But where the numbers are increasing, you got Arizona with nearly one out of four tests positive and at the same time you are increasing the number of tests, I can tell you with absolute certainty that's explosive spread of coronavirus,” Frieden added.

When asked to why the number of COVID-19 cases are exploding, but the number of deaths has dropped, Frieden said, “There are a few things going on. First off, deaths will lag cases by about a month. It takes some time for someone to feel sick, get hospitalized and, unfortunately, die.

“Second, the cases do appear to be in younger people now and the death rate is far, far, far lower in younger people than older, but as I said earlier, what starts in young adults, doesn't stay in young adults. So there may be a lag until we see cases. It's possible that older people are shielding themselves more and we are also getting better at caring for the disease at hospitals,” the former CDC director said.

“So the explosive spread isn't being followed yet by an explosive increase in deaths, but what we are seeing in some states already is a big increase in intensive care unit admissions and that's a sign that this is not benign, this is going to result in more deaths. We estimate in the next month we will see at least 15,000 more deaths in the U.S.,” he added.
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06/29/2020 - 10:13</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Melanie Arter</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cnsnews.com/2158975</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
