<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:schema="http://schema.org/" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.newsbusters.org/">
  <channel>
    <title>NewBusters Twitter Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>@CNN's @brianstelter Compares Trump's America to Soviet Union: 'What is the Cost of Lies?'</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/ryan-foley/2020/06/29/cnns-stelter-compares-trumps-america-soviet-union-what-cost-lies</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;CNN’s Brian Stelter kicked off Sunday’s edition of Reliable Sources with the usual foot-stomping editorial. He asked “what is the cost of lies?” Stelter noted that those were the first words of the HBO miniseries Chernobyl, which dramatized the 1986 nuclear disaster in the Soviet Union, a year after Stelter was born. After describing “secrecy, state deception, and endemic lying” as the main themes, Stelter proceeded to compare the Soviet Union to Trump’s America.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 3:14 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Ryan Foley</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258136</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>.@Facebook @finkd Caves to Liberal Pressure and Agrees to Censor @realDonaldTrump via @descarteslover</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/corinne-weaver/2020/06/29/facebook-caves-liberal-pressure-and-agrees-censor-trump</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg once said, “I don’t think it’s right for a private company to censor politicians or the news in a democracy.” The sentiment seemed to vanish after a slew of ad boycotts and hit pieces in the liberal media. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 2:27 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Corinne Weaver</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258146</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>CNN cheers John Roberts siding with left as choosing 'independence' 'integrity of the court' during an election year</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/kristine-marsh/2020/06/29/cnn-cheers-john-roberts-choosing-integrity-abortion-during</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite abortion being an issue which continues to divide Americans, CNN Newsroom cheered the Supreme&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 2:00 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Kristine Marsh</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258144</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Now #BLM wants to erase #StLouis, and they don't care who gets hurt. #AntiCatholic  via @Mattphilbin</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/matt-philbin/2020/06/29/st-louis-catholics-attacked-defending-statue-citys-namesake</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;You may not find many in business, universities, Congress or the Chief Justice of the United States’s office, but there are still Catholics out there willing to defend the Church, decency and civilization. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 1:43 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Matt Philbin</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258143</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>.@amandaseales Hosts BET Awards, 'Black Everything,' 'Karen-Free'</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/julie-mitchell/2020/06/29/bet-awards-host-imitates-karens-racist-skit</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;Just when you thought the BET awards could not get any more woke, the host performs a skit on video chat, pretending to be a white woman afraid of black people. But then again, what is the best way for BET to make their fan base feel victimized, while simultaneously promoting the marxist Black Lives Matter movement? &lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 1:30 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Julie Mitchell</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258142</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sickos at the @nytimes celebrate ripping statues down -- "Dumped, Painted, Toppled, Boxed Up, and Hoisted Away."</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/clay-waters/2020/06/29/ny-times-relishes-destruction-statues-avoids-mentioning-washington</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;The New York Times has openly relished ripping down and vandalizing statues, as demonstrated by the full-page photo essay on the front of the Friday National section under the suspiciously celebratory headline “Dumped, Painted, Toppled, Boxed Up and Hoisted Away.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 1:24 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Clay Waters</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258132</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>WHAT? Fox Streaming Platform Will Feature @LouisFarrakhan’s ‘Message’ from ‘God’ On July 4 @foxsoultv</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/gabriel-hays/2020/06/29/what-fox-streaming-platform-will-feature-farrakhans-message</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;As American society continues to convulse over the demands of politically-divisive, race-baiting groups like Black Lives Matter, one prominent TV network decided that showcasing a full speech from black supremacist and anti-semite Louis Farrakhan on the 4th of July would be a great idea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 1:11 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Gabriel Hays</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258141</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>President @realDonaldTrump Expects Twitter Ban, Calls for Big Tech Reform via @AlaxandairH</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/alexander-hall/2020/06/29/president-donald-trump-expects-twitter-ban-calls-big-tech</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;As the Trump administration initiates war on Big Tech censorship, President Donald Trump suspects that Silicon Valley liberals will use every dirty trick they can come up with, including censoring him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 1:06 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Alexander Hall</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258140</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Oh, now they love him. ABC cheers John Roberts for being above politics, "caring a great deal." </title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2020/06/29/picking-sides-abc-cheers-john-roberts-above-politics-cares-great</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;ABC journalists on Monday breathlessly broke in with live reaction to the Supreme Court striking down a Louisiana law restricting abortion. The pivotal fifth vote was provided by John Roberts who sided with the Court’s liberals. Of course, this mean that now Roberts “cares a great deal” about being apolitical. ABC also repeated Planned Parenthood talking points about the Court and 2020. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 12:23 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Scott Whitlock</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258137</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>The @washingtonpost scolds the youth of America for spreading COVID-19, but avoids scolding the protests.</title>
  <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/pj-gladnick/2020/06/29/washpost-scolds-youths-covid-spread-avoids-scolding-protests</link>
  <description>&lt;p&gt;The coronavirus cases have risen recently (while the daily deaths have fallen) in the United States. So who is to blame? The Washington Post points its finger at a number of groups while notably avoiding mention of one very left-wing cause which gathered in the thousands recently without practicing social distancing. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>June 29th, 2020 12:05 PM</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>P.J. Gladnick</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">258118</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
